<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-08-22T13:05:19-07:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/atom.xml</id><title type="html">BSidesSF</title><subtitle>Security BSides San Francisco is an annual information security conference. It is a conference by the community for the community.
</subtitle><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><entry><title type="html">BSidesSF 2025 Schedule, Registration, and Call for Volunteers</title><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2025/03/join-us" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BSidesSF 2025 Schedule, Registration, and Call for Volunteers" /><published>2025-03-05T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2025-03-05T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2025/03/join-us</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2025/03/join-us"><![CDATA[<h1 id="join-us">Join us</h1>

<p>BSidesSF is taking place on April 26 &amp; 27 with our theme <strong>Here Be Dragons</strong>. 
During these two days, we will come together as a community to advance the body of 
Information Security knowledge by providing a forum for education, collaboration, and continued conversation.</p>

<table>
<tr style="valign: top;">
<td style="vertical-align: top; padding: 7px;">
<h3>Call for Volunteers</h3>
Do you have a deep passion for interacting with our community? 
Please see our <a href="/volunteer">Volunteers</a> page for details about responsibilities and benefits.
<br />
<br />
<a href="https://bsidessf.org/volunteer">Learn More</a>
</td>


<td style="vertical-align: top; padding: 7px;">
<h3> Registration</h3>
Join the information security community for amazing sessions, workshops, villages, and a dragon-themed party!
<br />
<br />
<a href="https://bsidessf.regfox.com/2025">Register</a>
</td>


<td style="vertical-align: top; padding: 7px;">
<h3>Sponsorships</h3>
Thank you to our many sponsors who have supported us this year.
We appreciate your invaluable contributions that make this event successful.
<br />
<br />
<a href="https://bsidessf.org/sponsors">See Our Sponsors</a>
</td>
</tr>
</table>
<p><br /></p>

<p>Check out our amazing line-up of talks, workshops, and other events in our <a href="/schedule">schedule</a>.</p>

<p>We look forward to seeing you this year!</p>

<p>Many thanks,</p>

<p><em>The BSidesSF Organizers</em></p>]]></content><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><category term="post" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BSidesSF 2025 Call for Participation</title><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2024/10/call-for-papers-2025" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BSidesSF 2025 Call for Participation" /><published>2024-10-16T11:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2024-10-16T11:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2024/10/call-for-papers-2025</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2024/10/call-for-papers-2025"><![CDATA[<p>BSidesSF is excited to open the Call for Participation for the BSidesSF 2025
conference. The 2025 event will be held at City View at Metreon in San
Francisco on Saturday, April 26th &amp; Sunday, April 27th.</p>

<p>Our Call for Participation (CFP) process is fairly standard, but please do take
the time to read through the information, as there are changes every year.
<a href="/cfp">Read all about it here</a> and spread the word!</p>

<p>Additionally, we are always looking for more sponsors. If you are
interested, check out the <a href="/sponsors/benefits">sponsors benefits</a>
and reach out to us at <a href="mailto:sponsors@bsidessf.org">sponsors@bsidessf.org</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><category term="post" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[BSidesSF is excited to open the Call for Participation for the BSidesSF 2025 conference. The 2025 event will be held at City View at Metreon in San Francisco on Saturday, April 26th &amp; Sunday, April 27th.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BSidesSF 2024 Schedule, Registration, and Call for Volunteers</title><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2024/03/join-us" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BSidesSF 2024 Schedule, Registration, and Call for Volunteers" /><published>2024-03-11T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2024-03-11T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2024/03/join-us</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2024/03/join-us"><![CDATA[<h1 id="join-us">Join us</h1>

<p>BSidesSF is taking place on May 4 &amp; 5 with our theme <strong>You Can’t Spell Dystopia Without AI</strong>. 
During these two days, we will come together as a community to advance the body of 
Information Security knowledge by providing a forum for education, collaboration, and continued conversation.</p>

<table>
<tr style="valign: top;">
<td style="vertical-align: top; padding: 7px;">
<h3>Call for Volunteers</h3>
Do you have a deep passion for interacting with our community? Work a minimum of 1 General shift or 2 
Safety Ops shifts to get a free BSidesSF t-shirt &amp; badge.
<br />
<br />
<a href="https://bsidessf.org/volunteer">Learn More</a>
</td>



<td style="vertical-align: top; padding: 7px;">


<h3> Registration</h3>
Join the information security community for amazing sessions, workshops, villages, and a dystopian-themed party!
<br />
<br />
<a href="https://bsidessf.regfox.com/2024">Register</a>

</td>


<td style="vertical-align: top; padding: 7px;">

<h3>Sponsorships</h3>
BSidesSF is a volunteer and sponsor supported event.
<br />
<br />
Scholarship, Sunday Daytime Bar, Happy Hour, Headshots, and Wi-Fi sponsorships are still available.
<br />
<br />
<a href="https://bsidessf.org/sponsors">Sponsor Now</a>
</td>
</tr>
</table>

<h4 id="highlighted-sessions">Highlighted Sessions</h4>

<ul>
  <li><em>Kelly Thibault</em> and <em>Lisa Hall</em> on “Why Everyone Hates Vulnerability Management &amp; How to Make Better”</li>
  <li><em>Clint Gibler</em> on “TL;DR: Applying AI to Security”</li>
  <li><em>Adrian Sanabria</em> on “AI: Best Janitor or Worst Superhero?”</li>
  <li><em>Mukund Sarma, Jeevan Singh, Ariel Shin, Jacob Salassi and Julia Knecht</em> on “Titans of Scale: Strategies to Scale Security in Expanding Organizations”</li>
</ul>

<p>Check out these and the rest of our amazing line-up of talks, workshops and other events in our <a href="/schedule">schedule</a>.</p>

<p>We look forward to seeing you this year!</p>

<p>Many thanks,</p>

<p>The BSidesSF Organizers</p>]]></content><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><category term="post" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BSidesSF 2024 Call for Participation</title><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2023/10/call-for-papers-2024" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BSidesSF 2024 Call for Participation" /><published>2023-10-22T17:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-10-22T17:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2023/10/call-for-papers-2024</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2023/10/call-for-papers-2024"><![CDATA[<p>BSidesSF is excited to open the Call for Participation for the BSidesSF 2024 conference. The 2024 event will be held at City View at Metreon in San Francisco on Saturday, May 4th &amp; Sunday, May 5th.</p>

<p>Our Call for Participation process is fairly standard, but please do take the time to read through the information, as there are changes every year.</p>

<p>To all of you who think you have something to say – take a look and get writing. You have until December 11th to make your submission.</p>

<p>For complete details and information on how to submit, check out the <a href="/cfp">Call for Participation</a>.</p>

<p>Spread the word!</p>]]></content><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[BSidesSF is excited to open the Call for Participation for the BSidesSF 2024 conference. The 2024 event will be held at City View at Metreon in San Francisco on Saturday, May 4th &amp; Sunday, May 5th.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BSidesSF 2023 Registration Now Open!</title><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2023/02/registration-open" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BSidesSF 2023 Registration Now Open!" /><published>2023-02-23T11:30:00-08:00</published><updated>2023-02-23T11:30:00-08:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2023/02/registration-open</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2023/02/registration-open"><![CDATA[<p>We’re back again - registration for BSidesSF 2023 is now open! Get your tickets here: <a href="https://bsidessf.regfox.com/2023">https://bsidessf.regfox.com/2023</a> and join us Saturday, April 22nd and Sunday, April 23rd. Workshop slots are first come, first serve, so if you’re interested, sign-up while seats are still available.</p>

<p>All tickets include breakfast both days, multiple drinks, and admission to the awesome Saturday Night Party!</p>

<p>Want to know what’s going on? Check out the <a href="/schedule">full schedule</a>.</p>

<p>See you in late April ~</p>]]></content><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back again - registration for BSidesSF 2023 is now open! Get your tickets here: https://bsidessf.regfox.com/2023 and join us Saturday, April 22nd and Sunday, April 23rd. Workshop slots are first come, first serve, so if you’re interested, sign-up while seats are still available.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BSidesSF 2023 Call for Presentations</title><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2022/10/call-for-papers-2023" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BSidesSF 2023 Call for Presentations" /><published>2022-10-13T12:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-10-13T12:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2022/10/call-for-papers-2023</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2022/10/call-for-papers-2023"><![CDATA[<p>BSidesSF is excited to open the Call for Presentations for the BSidesSF 2023 conference. The 2023 event will be held at City View at Metreon in San Francisco on Saturday, April 22nd &amp; Sunday, April 23rd.</p>

<p>Our Call for Presentations process is fairly standard, but please do take the time to read through the information, as there are changes every year.</p>

<p>To all of you who think you have something to say – take a look and get writing. You have until January 8th to make your submission.</p>

<p>For complete details and information on how to submit, check out the <a href="/cfp">Call for Presentations</a>.</p>

<p>Spread the word!</p>]]></content><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[BSidesSF is excited to open the Call for Presentations for the BSidesSF 2023 conference. The 2023 event will be held at City View at Metreon in San Francisco on Saturday, April 22nd &amp; Sunday, April 23rd.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to BSidesSF 2022</title><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2022/05/welcome-to-bsidessf" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to BSidesSF 2022" /><published>2022-05-31T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-05-31T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2022/05/welcome-to-bsidessf</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2022/05/welcome-to-bsidessf"><![CDATA[<p>The final countdown is on to BSidesSF 2022 – this Saturday, June 4th &amp; Sunday, June 5th!</p>

<p>We want to ensure everybody’s participation is amazing, so please read below for important information concerning this year’s event.</p>

<h3 id="getting-to-the-event">Getting to the Event</h3>

<p>We are back once again at the Metreon located at 135 4th Street in downtown San Francisco. The location of the Metreon lends itself to a few different transportation options. For those looking to take BART or Muni, the Metreon is located about a block from the Powell Street station. For those interested in taking Caltrain, the Metreon is one mile from the King Street station. For those driving, the Fifth and Mission Parking Garage is located directly across 4th Street and offers 24-hour parking.</p>

<p>Once at the Metreon, enter from the Yerba Buena Gardens north entrance (behind Lemonade if you’re coming from Mission Street).</p>

<p>After entering, take the stairs, escalators, or elevator up to the Mezzanine level for registration. The event will be distributed throughout the AMC Metreon 16 located on the third floor and the City View event space located on the fourth floor. However, you must first register on the Mezzanine to have access to these areas. To expedite registration, please have your QR code and proof of vaccination with ID ready.</p>

<p>If you pre-purchased a t-shirt or other merchandise, these will be available for pick up on the fourth floor (City View) at Coat Check beginning at 11am on Saturday. Please make sure you have your registration QR code ready for scanning.</p>

<h3 id="before-you-attend">Before You Attend</h3>

<p>Before you attend the event, we ask that you review our <a href="/about/code-of-conduct">Code of Conduct</a>, our <a href="/about/photo-policy">Photo and Video Policies</a>, and our <a href="/about/covid-19-safety-policy">COVID-19 Safety Policy</a>. We require that all guests abide by our policies and show respect and tolerance for each other’s uniqueness. We have no tolerance for physical, verbal, or sexual harassment; intimidation; or marginalization of any human! Additionally, due to venue restrictions, please note we only allow service animals at the event and will not be able to store bikes or scooters within the venue.</p>

<p>To summarize our <a href="/about/covid-19-safety-policy">COVID-19 Safety Policy</a> (please review the entire policy):</p>
<ul>
  <li>Proof of completed vaccination is required. Medical, religious, or philosophical objections will not be accepted. We also highly recommend that if you are eligible that you have received at least one booster dose.</li>
  <li>The name on your ID and your proof of vaccination must match.</li>
  <li>Masks must be worn at all times while indoors at the event, except when you are 1) actively eating or drinking; or 2) a presenter actively giving your talk/workshop. Masks must be worn completely over both your mouth and nose.</li>
  <li>If you feel sick, please don’t come.</li>
  <li>We highly recommend you self-test at home prior to coming.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="two-full-days-of-talks-events-and-happenings">Two Full Days of Talks, Events, and Happenings</h3>

<p>Doors will open at 9am and talks begin at 10am. The full schedule of events can be found on <a href="https://bsidessf2022.sched.com/">Sched</a> and HackerTracker (on Android and iOS). All talks, villages, and the CTF are open to any and all participants; if there is an open seat, it’s yours. For questions during talks, we will be using <a href="slido.com">Slido</a> with code #BSidesSF2022.</p>

<p>We encourage all participants to take a stroll through the Participant Hall and visit all our sponsors, without whom this event would not be possible. Many of our sponsors are actively recruiting, so we encourage you to stop by their booths to learn more if you are interested in new opportunities. We’ll be raffling off some really awesome items, so make sure to get your Sponsor Passport stamped and turned in prior to the daily raffle (12:30-1pm each day).</p>

<h3 id="event-wifi">Event WiFi</h3>

<p>We support both 802.1x EAP and WPA2 PSK.</p>

<div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>EAP SSID: BSidesSF
User: bsides
Password: bsides
</code></pre></div></div>

<div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>WPA2 SSID: BSidesSF-Static
WPA2 Key: bsidessf
</code></pre></div></div>

<p>Visit <a href="https://wifi.bsidessf.org">https://wifi.bsidessf.org</a> to download the EAP CA, iOS profile, and for more information.</p>

<p>We are looking forward to seeing you this Saturday! If you have any questions, please contact info@bsidessf.org.</p>

<p>Until then,</p>

<p>The BSidesSF Staff</p>]]></content><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><category term="post" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The final countdown is on to BSidesSF 2022 – this Saturday, June 4th &amp; Sunday, June 5th!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BSidesSF 2022 moving to June</title><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2021/12/moving-to-june-2022" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BSidesSF 2022 moving to June" /><published>2021-12-23T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-12-23T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2021/12/moving-to-june-2022</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2021/12/moving-to-june-2022"><![CDATA[<p>Following RSA Conference’s <a href="https://www.rsaconference.com/library/press-release/rsa-conference-2022-moves-to-june">announcement</a>, the organizers of BSidesSF have decided to move our 2022 event to align with RSAC’s new dates in June. Our updated 2022 dates therefore will be <strong>June 4-5, 2022</strong> still held at City View of Metreon in downtown San Francisco, CA.</p>

<p>Our goal continues to be bookending RSAC (holding our event the weekend before), as we appreciate the overlap in participants this affords us. Additionally, with the rise in COVID-19 cases due to the Omicron variant, we feel not hosting an in-person event during this tumultuous time is in the best interest of our community.</p>

<p>We understand this is a sudden disruption, especially with the conference so close at hand. The pandemic has unfortunately caused a lot of unpredictability with hosting in-person events.</p>

<p>We are actively working to notify all participants, presenters, sponsors, villages, volunteers, and vendors regarding the postponement and will be updating our websites and social media outlets as soon as information is available.</p>

<p>We hope you will still be able to join us in June.</p>

<p>Best,</p>

<p>The BSidesSF Staff</p>]]></content><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><category term="post" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following RSA Conference’s announcement, the organizers of BSidesSF have decided to move our 2022 event to align with RSAC’s new dates in June. Our updated 2022 dates therefore will be June 4-5, 2022 still held at City View of Metreon in downtown San Francisco, CA.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BSidesSF 2022 Registration Now Open!</title><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2021/12/registration-open" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BSidesSF 2022 Registration Now Open!" /><published>2021-12-17T19:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-12-17T19:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2021/12/registration-open</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2021/12/registration-open"><![CDATA[<p>We’re back again (and in-person!) - registration for BSidesSF 2022 is now open! Get your tickets here: <a href="https://bsidessf.regfox.com/2022">https://bsidessf.regfox.com/2022</a> and join us Saturday, <del>February 5th</del> June 4th and Sunday, <del>February 6th</del> June 5th. Workshop slots are first come, first serve, so if you’re interested, sign-up while seats are still available.</p>

<p>All tickets include breakfast both days, multiple drinks, and admission to the awesome Saturday Night Party!</p>

<p>Want to know what’s going on? Check out the <a href="/schedule">full schedule</a>.</p>

<p>See you in early <del>February</del> June ~</p>]]></content><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back again (and in-person!) - registration for BSidesSF 2022 is now open! Get your tickets here: https://bsidessf.regfox.com/2022 and join us Saturday, February 5th June 4th and Sunday, February 6th June 5th. Workshop slots are first come, first serve, so if you’re interested, sign-up while seats are still available.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Call for Volunteers at BSidesSF 2022</title><link href="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2021/12/call-for-volunteers" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Call for Volunteers at BSidesSF 2022" /><published>2021-12-07T20:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-12-07T20:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2021/12/call-for-volunteers</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bsidessf.org/a/2025/news/2021/12/call-for-volunteers"><![CDATA[<p>Interested in helping at BSidesSF 2022?</p>

<p>BSidesSF is a 100% volunteer-run event and simply wouldn’t be possible without the help of our awesome community. If you’re interested in helping, take a look at <a href="/volunteer">our volunteer page</a> for current openings. In exchange for at least six hours of your time, you’ll receive free admission and meals during the conference.</p>

<p>If you have any questions, please contact volunteer [@] bsidessf.org or join <a href="https://bsidessf.slack.com/messages/C0CSQ1TTN">#volunteers on our Slack</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>BSidesSF</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interested in helping at BSidesSF 2022?]]></summary></entry></feed>